这是什么
Help me out, what is this?
扭扭虫
Googlie Worm.
这个呢
And this?
霓虹泡泡毛球
Glow Pop Jiggly Jam.
太逗了
It's so funny!
这是什么
What's this?
去年剩的一块三明治
A hunk of sandwich from last year.
盖勒钓到了  看来是条大鱼
Geller's got one hooked! Looks like a big one!
经典的人鱼大战...
It's the classic struggle between man...
不知是谁撞倒了台灯
Someone knocked over a lamp.
知道今年去钓鱼时  最妙之处是什么吗
You guys know what'll be great about the fishing trip this year?
每次到了湖心我爸都会问我
When my dad ask me in the middle of the lake, give me that,
"你最近都在忙什么"之类的问题
"Joey, what are you doing with your life?" stuff,
这次我可以说  我要跟查尔顿·赫斯顿演电影
I can say, "Well, I'm doing a movie with Charlton Heston, dad.
你在忙些什么呢
What are you doing with your life?"
怎么我一出来你们就不说笑了
You don't have to stop having fun just because I'm here.
凯西又没有背叛你们所有人
Kathy didn't cheat on all of you.
当然  除了你
Well, except you.
乔伊  你不该丢下钱德去钓鱼
Hey Joey, I don't think you should leave Chandler alone.
他跟凯西才分手两天
It's only been 2 days since he broke up with Kathy.
下周再去钓鱼吧
Maybe you should go fishing next week.
可我现在又帮不上忙
Look. There's nothing I can do for him right now.
他还穿着运动裤
He's still in his sweats.
这才是第一阶段
That's only phase one.
等他到第二阶段的时候我就回来了
I'll be back for phase two.
我从不错过第二阶段
I'd never miss that.
什么第二阶段
What's phase two?
喝个烂醉  去脱衣舞俱乐部
Getting drunk and going to a strip club.
那样怎么会有帮助
How does going to a strip clab make him better?
那里有裸女
There are naked ladies there.
这有助于他过渡到第三阶段
And it helps to get to phase three:
对别的女人产生性幻想
picturing yourself with other women.
那个阶段也有裸女
There are naked ladies there too.
就不能让我清静一小会儿吗
Would you give me one minute, please?
这是跟上周你挑的外套搭配的吗
So these will match the jacket you picked out for me last week?
这就对了
There we go.
就是这样
There it is.
知道我还需要什么吗  手套
You know what I need? Gloves.
棕色的皮手套
Brown leather dress gloves.
好  我看看
Oh, okay, well, let's see...
这只手是大号
You are about...this one is large.
这只手
And this one...
也是大号
Also large?
对  一副大号手套马上送来
Two larges' coming right up.
-瑞秋  耽误你一下好吗  -没问题
- Rachel, could I have a moment? -Sure.
我侄女从伦敦过来玩
I was wondering, my niece, you see, is in town from London.
是从什罗普郡  你懂的
Shropshire really, but you know.
她跟你差不多大
She's about your age, I'd say.
总之  我有两张歌剧《蝙蝠》的票
Anyway, I have tickets for the opera. Die Fledermaus.
你愿意今晚陪她去看吗
And I was wondering if you'd like to keep her company this evening?
好  没问题
Sure. You got it!
太棒了  算上我  我  《蝙蝠》  很好
Great, count me in. Me. Fledermaus. Great! I really...
不打扰两位了  谢谢  太感谢了
Yes, of course. Thank you. Thank you so very much.
-接下来  -接下来
- So?  - So?
-手套  -对了  不好意思  我马上去拿
- Gloves? - Right. Sorry, I'll be right back.
其实  我该走了
Actually, you know what, I gotta take off.
不过  不知道你今晚有没有事
But I was curious. Do you have any plan for tonight?
没有  没事
No, nothing!
我投资了一家夜总会
I invested in this nightclub.
今晚开幕  你要去吗
And it's open tonight. Would you like to come?
好啊  太棒了
Yeah! That would be great!
我猜你很喜欢性虐待的主题吧
You're into hard-core S&M, right?
-应该...   -我开玩笑的
- Well, I guess... - I'm kidding.
我会先到  我会把你列为贵宾
I gotta get there early, but I'll put you on the VIP list.
你来了就找我
Look for me.
好  没问题
Yeah. Great! You bet.
-晚上见  -好的
- I'll see you tonight. - OK!
-差点忘了给你票  -什么
- I almost forgot the tickets, didn't I. - What?
你和艾蜜莉  今晚看《蝙蝠》
For you and Emily. Tonight. Die Fledermaus.
噢  对
Oh, right.
你一定会喜欢的  三大男高音去了两个
I think you'll like it. It has two out of the three tenors.
棒极了
Oh yeah.
凯西居然这样对我
I can't believe Kathy did this to me.
我真的以为她就是我的归宿
I really thought she was the one.
我宣布
I'll tell you what.
从现在起  我再也不离开这张椅子了
From now on, I'm not getting out of this chair. Ever!
以后这张椅子就是我的归宿了
From now on, this chair is the one!
如果还有的话  就是这条运动裤
You know what else is the one? My sweatpants.
别这样  兄弟  把运动裤脱掉
Come on, man. Just take the sweats off, okay?
脱掉吧  我们来玩点好玩的
Just take them off and we'll have some fun.
钓到大鱼了吗
Catch any big fish?
说出来吓死你们
Oh my god! You guys have no idea.
-你好臭  -搞什么
- You stink! - Are you kidding?
在湖上漂了三天  我一直没洗澡
Yeah, three days on the lake without a shower.
而且  还掉进了一大桶鱼饵里
Plus! I fell in that big tub of worms at the bait stand!
他怎么样
How's he doing?
在那椅子里呆坐了整整两天
He hasn't left that chair in two days.
兄弟  你还好吗
Hey, buddy, how's it going?
看到没  好兄弟回家就没事了
You see? He just needed his pal to come home.
我得去背台词了
I got to memorize my lines.
明天一早要和查尔顿·赫斯顿对戏
Me and Charlton Heston, bright and early tomorrow, baby!
莫妮卡
Hey, Monica.
你怎么了
What's the matter?
约书亚约我今晚去参加高级夜总会开业典礼
Joshua invited me to this fancy club opening tonight.
但我已经答应沃森先生
But I already told Mr. Waltham...
要陪他的侄女去看老掉牙的歌剧
that I would take his niece to the dumb old opera.
唉  我能怎么办呢
So, what are you going to do?
-我也不知道  宝贝  -不行  救救我
- I don't know, sweetie. - No! Help me!
-我没空啊  还得上班呢  -菲比呢
- I can't. I have to work. - Phoebe?
我很想  但我都在晚上晨吐
I would, but I get my morning sickness in the evening.
也行  除非她想整晚
No, unless she wants to spend the night
帮我捞住头发
holding my hair back for me.
拜托啦  我一定要去找约书亚
You guys, come on! This is...I have to meet Joshua.
这样他才有机会看到有趣的瑞秋
This is my one chance for him to see the "fun" Rachel.
"如果她是我老婆就好了"的瑞秋
The "wouldn't it be great if she were my wife?" Rachel.
乔伊和钱德勒回来了吗
Are Joey and Chandler back?
钱德勒还在第一阶段
Chandler's still in phase one,
而乔伊就是你闻到的臭味的来源
and Joey's that thing you smell.
-你好  -你好啊
- Hi. -Hi.
帮帮忙吧...
So...
不要
No.
拜托啦
Come on!
-应该是她  -等一下
- Think she's here. - No. Wait, wait.
罗斯  拜托啦
Ross, please?
你要我带一个陌生女孩去看歌剧
You want me to take some girl I've never met to the opera...
好让你去夜总会跟某个男人打情骂俏
so you can go to a club and flirt with some guy?
真难决定啊
That is a toughie.
她到走廊了
She's looking down the hall.
她直勾勾地盯着我呢
She looked right at me.
透过猫眼是看不到的  对吧
You can't see people through that hole, can you?
-你好啊  -你好啊
- Hello. - Hello.
马上就来  罗斯  拜托啦
I'll be right there! Okay, Ross, please, come on.
我觉得我们应该都已经走出来了
I thought we had moved on.
我觉得我们已经可以彼此祝福了
I thought we come to a place where we could be happy for each other.
难道只有我走出来了
I mean, was that just me?
好吧  我带她去
All right, I'll do it.
谢谢你  谢谢
Thank you, thank you.
-艾蜜莉  -我是
- Emily. - Yes.
我是瑞秋·格林
I'm Rachel Green.
谢天谢地
Thank goodness!
计划有小小的变动
There's been a teeny teeny change of plans.
我今晚临时有事...所以...
Turns out I'm not free tonight...so...
是吗
Really?
太好了  我一定是没接到电话
That's just lovely, isn't it. I must've missed your call,
虽然我整天都没出门
even though I didn't leave the flat all day.
我
Well, l...
不  这也没什么
No no no. That's not rude.
自打我来到这里就诸事不顺...
It's perfectly in keeping with the trip...
先是被你们的热狗车撞倒
where I've already been run down by one of your wiener cars...
在肯尼迪国际机场又被脱衣服搜身
and been strip-searched at John F. Kennedy Airport,
你们美国人显然认为
apparently to you people,
我长得就像屁股里
I look like someone who's got a balloon full of cocaine
塞了可卡因的人
stuffed up their bum.
我觉得你很漂亮啊
I think you look great.
晚安  很高兴认识你们
Good night. It was very nice to meet you all.
我去追她
I'll get her.
快去吧
Please, hurry.
他们讲话好好玩
Don't you just love the way they talk?
-怎么了  -宝宝在踢我
- What? - It kicked, I think the baby kicked!
天啊
Oh, my God.
不对  是内裤的松紧带断了
No, wait. The elastic in my underwear busted.
完了  我睡过头了
Oh, my God! I overslept!
半小时前就应该到的
I was supposed to be on the set a half an hour ago!
我得赶快
I gotta get out of here!
乔伊  你不能这样去  你臭死了
Oh wait, Joey, you can't go like that! You stink!
我没洗澡就睡过去了
Look, I know I feel asleep before I could shower
现在没时间了
and now I don't have time!
才十条街  跑过去还来得及
It's just 10 blocks away. If I run, I can make it.
跑十条街  那你不是更臭了吗
Run 10 blocks. That'll help the smell.
慢一点  不  快走吧
Slow down! No, keep moving.
昨晚怎么样啊
How did it go with Joshua last night?
我没见到约书亚
Well, I didn't see Joshua.
但我照着一个女孩的脸给了一拳
But I did punch a girl in the face.
-什么  -什么
- What? - What?
昨晚真的很倒霉  大雨倾盆
The whole night was horrible. It was pouring down raining.
而到现场我却发现名单上没有瑞秋·格林
And when I got there, there was no Rachel Greene on the list.
但有一个瑞秋·格皮
But there was a Rachel Greep.
那你见到她了吗
So did you get to meet her?
根本没这个人
No. There is no Rachel Greep.
但有个女生听到了
But then, this other girl overheard us.
大叫"我就是瑞秋·格皮"
And she was all, "I'm Rachel Greep! I'm Rachel Greep!"
结果门卫就让她进去了
And he let her right in.
然后你就打了她的脸
So you hit her in the face?
打不着了  她已经进去了
No, she was already in.
可后来我身后一个五大三粗的婆娘
But then this big bitch behind me
要偷我的伞...
tried to steal my umbrella...
我就给了她点颜色瞧瞧
so I clocked her.
真是的  我只想在工作之余
I can't believe this. All I wanted was just a few hours...
跟约书亚相处一下
outside of work to see Joshua...
好让他有机会爱上我
so that he could go ahead and start falling in love with me.
菲
Pheebs.
那是你的名字
Honey, that's your name.
原来这是菲比的简称啊
That's short for Phoebe?
我以为那是我们之间的爱称
I thought that's what we called each other.
-你穿上裤子了  -没错
- You're wearing pants! - That's right.
我那几位兄弟呢
Where are the guys?
我准备好借酒消愁和看脱衣舞了
I'm ready to get drunk and see strippers.
才早上9点半
It's 9:30 in the morning.
那里的早餐是自助式的
They got a breakfast buffet.
你好  是罗斯啊
Hello. Oh, hey, Ross!
让我和他说
Let me talk to him!
-天哪  -我能不能...
- Oh, my God! - Can't I just...?
等等  你说什么
Wait, what?
她嘘我  那是我的电话  她还嘘我
She shushs me. It's my phone and she's shush...
别吵
Please!
他说什么
What's he saying?
他跟艾蜜莉投宿在佛蒙特  在一起吃早餐呢
He's with Emily at a Bed and Breakfast in Vermont!
什么  天哪
What? Oh, my God!
艾蜜莉是谁  不会吧
Who the hell is Emily...? No.
他们在佛蒙特  怎么会
They're in Vermont? How was this happen?
他怎么会跟那个丑巫婆去佛蒙特
How...how did he end up in Vermont with that awful witch?!
也许因为她没有一直打他吧
Maybe she doesn't hit him all the time.
罗斯  快来
Ross, come quickly.
外面有只驯鹿在吃果园的水果
There's a deer just outside eating fruit from the orchard!
我要挂了
I got to go!
外面有只驯鹿在吃果园的水果
There's a deer just outside eating fruit from the orchard!
他挂了
He had to go.
外面有只驯鹿在吃果园的水果
There was a deer just outside eating fruit from the orchard.
我真不理解  她那么难看
I don't get this. She was horrible!
我站到那边去好了
I'm going to go stand over there.
你干嘛这么在乎
Why do you care so much anyway?
我才不在乎
I don't care.
我只是因为自己跟约书亚没进展而懊恼
I'm just upset that I'm getting nowhere with Joshua.
但怎么也不应该刚一认识
You know what, still, you do not just meet someone
就一起跑去佛蒙特啊
and go flitting off to Vermont!
你和贝利不是刚一认识就跑去维尔了吗
When you first met Barry, you flitted off to Vail.
你能不能偶尔有一次
Could you, just for once...
不要什么小事都记那么清楚吗
not remember every little thing?
他什么时候回来
So you know, when's he getting back?
过一两天吧
A couple of days.
我就知道会这样
I knew something like this would gonna happen.
你干什么
What are you doing?
钱德勒  你的阶段不能倒退的呀
Chandler. You can't just go back a phase!
有何不可  你指的是时间的概念
Yes, you can. You're thinking about time.
时间才不能倒流
You can't go back in time.
我们跟你去进行第二阶段好了
Why don't you do your phase two strip club thing with us?
对呀  我们可以当你的好兄弟
Yeah, come on, we can be guys!
你们不行
No, you can't.
让我们当嘛  我们很想试试当男人的感觉
Let us be guys! Maybe we want to be guys.
可千万别这么想
No, you don't want to be guys.
全身是毛还短命
You'd be all hairy and wouldn't live as long.
能不能别这么懦弱  把运动裤脱掉
Would you just stop being such a wuss and get those off?
跟我们去看裸女跳舞
And come with us and watch naked girls dance around!
好吧
Okay.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我是乔伊·崔比安尼  我来了
Joey Tribbiani. I'm here. I'm here.
别急  来得及  进度有点滞后
Calm down, we got time. We're running a little late.
准备就绪
All set.
你看  查尔顿·赫斯顿在嚼甘草糖
Look at that. Charlton Heston eating licorice.
他很爱嚼甘草糖  从没见过他...
Yeah, he loves them. I've never seen him with...
搞什么  什么东西这么臭
What the hell is that? What smells so bad?
是你
You?
你这么想不奇怪  不过你知道到底是谁吗
I could see why you would think that. But you know who it is?
是你
You.
不  是赫斯顿
No, no. It's Heston.
什么
What?
他臭得好像去钓了三天鱼
The man reeks like he went on a three-day fishing trip,
然后还嚼甘草
and then ate licorice.
不可能
There's no way he smells.
只有他的休息室里有浴室
He's the only one around here with a shower in his dressing room.
真的  有浴室
Really? A shower?
是哪一间
And...which room might that be?
门口写着"赫斯顿"的那间
The one with "Heston" on it.
有意思
Interesting.
我换了零钞  你要不要去塞她的小裤裤里
I got some ones. You want to put them in her panties?
不用了  娘
No, thanks, Mom!
噢  不行  那烟
Oh, no. That.
你得熄掉  因为我是孕妇
You have to put that out because I'm pregnant.
也许你和你的孩子应该去别家脱衣舞俱乐部
Maybe you and your baby ought to go to another strip club.
这才不是我的孩子
It's not my baby.
很好
Very good.
太棒了  我喜欢  很火辣
Really good. I enjoyed it. Very exotic.
我查过留言  约书亚没打来
I just checked our messages and Joshua didn't call.
我还以为
You'd think he'd be worried about me
我没出现在现场  他会担心呢
not showing up in his club.
更糟的是
You know what makes it so much worse?
罗斯正在佛蒙特风流快活
Ross is all happy in Vermont.
拜托  你可是在看脱衣舞
Come on, look where you are!
再来一轮得其利酒
Another round of daiquiris.
别忘了  我要汽水  谢谢
Remember, virgin for me, please.
记得提醒我去问那个人的名字
Don't let me leave without the name of that carpet guy.
拜托
Come on!
算了  我要回家给凯西打电话
You know what? I'll go home and call Kathy.
也许是个好办法
Oh, I think it'll help.
错  我这是在考验你们
No. That was a test.
再过几小时我会烂醉
In a couple hours, I'll be really drunk.
我就会想给她打电话  你们可得阻止我
I'm gonna wanna to call Kathy. You'll have to stop me.
而再之后我就会醉得完全失去理智
And then after that I'll be so drunk,
甚至想给珍妮丝打电话
I'm gonna want to call Janice.
你是该打  她还好吗
You should! How is she?
有人需要再看一次大腿舞
I think somebody needs another lap dance.
有人吗  谁在里面
Hello. Who's in there?
你好吗
How you doing?
见鬼  你是谁
Who in the hell are you?
我说柯克·道格拉斯你不会信吧
Guess you wouldn't believe me if I said I was Kirk Douglas?
把裤子穿上  我好踹你的屁股
Put some pants on, kid, so I can kick your butt.
不  等等  你有所不知
No, wait. You don't understand.
我是个演员
I'm an actor.
我叫乔伊·崔比安尼  今天要跟你对戏
Joey Tribbiani. I'm doing a scene with you today.
但是我很臭[演得很烂]
And I stink!
你也参演这部影片吗
You're in this picture?
对  我演其中一名不肯跟你合作的警察
I'm one of the cops who won't work with you
因为你太我行我素
because you're a loose cannon.
总之我很抱歉
Anyway, look, I'm really sorry.
但我真的很臭[演得很烂]
But I just...I stink.
-乔伊是吧  -对
- Joey, right? -Yeah.
每个演员总有时候
Every actor, one time or another...
会觉得自己很烂[很臭]
every actor thinks he stinks.
连劳伦斯·奥利弗有时也会这么想
Even Laurence Olivier sometimes thought he stank.
而劳勃·瑞福压根不看自己的片子
Bob Redford won't even watch himself.
不  我不是这个意思
No, no, no. You don't understand.
听我说完
Listen to me.
每一个好演员
I don't know one actor worth his salt...
在演艺生涯中都曾说过"天哪  我真烂"
who, one time in his career, didn't say, "God, I stink!"
我刚拍完一场戏
I just did a scene out there.
第一遍我演得烂透了
First take, I stunk the place up.
重要的是  你要记住
But, the important thing, and you must remember...
不管你认为自己有多烂
no matter how badly you think you stink...
也不能进我的休息室
you must never, ever bust into my dressing room
用我的浴室
and use my shower!
懂了吗
Do you understand me?
-是  很抱歉  -等等
- Yes, sir. I'm very sorry. - Wait a minute!
把裤子带走
Take your pants.
难以置信  他居然还没打来
I can't believe it! He still hasn't called..
谁  乔旭吗
Who, Josh?
是约书亚
It's Joshua.
他不喜欢别人叫他乔旭吗
What? He doesn't like "Josh"?
是我不喜欢
No, I don't.
我要把运动裤换回来
All right. I'm going to put my sweats back on.
不要啦  你说得对
No! Wait, wait. You know what? You were right.
我们当男生当得不好  知道原因吗
We really weren't great at being guys. You know why?
因为我们是女生
Because we're girls.
-你知道女生最擅长什么  -跳脱衣舞
- You know what girls are really good at? - Stripping!
不  是倾听
No, listening!
坐下
Sit.
如果你肯一吐为快  或许就没事了
Maybe it just would really, really help if you would just talk.
是啊  你心里到底在想什么
Yeah, come on. What's going on in there?
你想哭也没关系  哭吧
And you know, if you want to cry, that's okay too.
别这样  再这样我只能请你们都离开
I'm going to have to ask you all to leave.
钱德勒
Chandler.
算了  我们试过了  但第三阶段没希望了
Forget it. We tried, but phase three is a lost cause.
那些舞娘都很火辣
Those strippers were insanely hot,
我却无法产生性幻想
and I couldn't picture myself with any of them.
她们真的很漂亮
They really were pretty, weren't they?
-我喜欢演飞行员的那位  -糖糖吗
- I really liked that fighter pilot one. - Candy?
她真是生气蓬勃
She was so spunky!
要是我要跟女人在一起...
I think if I were going to be with a woman...
我会选蜜雪儿那型的
it'd be with someone like Michelle.
她好娇小
She was just so petite.
不知道  不过我觉得我会选香塔儿
See, I don't know. For me, it would have to be Chantal.
-香塔儿  -天呐
- Chantal! - Oh my God.
她皮肤好嫩啊
She had the smoothest skin.
我塞钱给她时  手擦过她的丁字裤和大腿
I stuck that dollar bill in her G-string and grazed her thigh...
第三阶段  我进入第三阶段了
Phase three! I just achieved phase three!
真的吗
Really?
我的脑海中出现了你们跟她们在一起的画面
I am totally picturing you with all those women!
那可不是第三阶段
That's-that's not Phase Three.
那幅画面中  我也在场
Well, I'm there too!
我们在开性爱派对吗
Are we all together like in a group?
别说了  我想得快疯了
Stop it, you're killing me!
我进入第四阶段了
I think I moved on to phase four!
那是什么
What is that?  What is that?
我再也不想谈恋爱了
I don't want a relationship ever!
只想跟脱衣舞娘和朋友上床
I just want sex with strippers and my friends!
来嘛
Come on.
让我看看你的笑容
Let me see that smile.
我不想笑
I don't want to.
拜托啦
Please?
人家也想去脱衣舞俱乐部嘛
I wanted to go to the strip club!
你有的是机会
You'll gonna have plenty of chances.
世上有成千上万的女人
There are thousands of women out there,
排着队等着伤我的心呢
who are just waiting to screw me over.
好吧
Yeah, all right.
佛蒙特之旅怎样
How was Vermont?
艾蜜莉真是...太棒了
Emily is...incredible.
她好得无法形容
There are no words to describe her.
整个周末就像一场美梦
The whole weekend was like a dream.
还有你  瑞秋
And you! Rach!
你说得一点也没错
You were so right.
什么
What?
你说过  我们总算到了一个
What you said about us finally being in a place...
可以彼此祝福的阶段
where we could really be happy for each other.
我原本还没完全走出来
I admit, I wasn't quite there.
想到你和那个乔旭...
The thought of you and that Josh guy...
约书亚
Joshua.
跟约书亚在俱乐部里跳舞狂欢
Joshua guy at that club, dancing, having a good time.
我就觉得
And the thought of it kind of...
你懂吗  但现在
You know? But now!
我完全走出来了
But now, I'm totally there.
我终于跟你一样了
I'm finally where you are.
谢天谢地
Thank goodness!
谢谢你把艾蜜莉介绍给我
And thank you for Emily.
不客气  我很乐意帮忙
No problem. I'm so glad I could help, you know?
真替你开心
I'm happy for you.
我也替你开心
Happy for you.
不  是我替你开心
Oh, no, happy for you.
好  接下来是这样
All right. Here's what we'll do.
你帮我脱衣服
You are going to take off my clothes.
你们两个去拿精油
You two, go get the oils.
你就一直扯着脖子叫嚷
And you, just constantly scream at the top of your voice,
"吾王钱德勒万岁!"
"Chandler's the king! Chandler's the king!"
我想跟她在一起  我喜欢她
I want to be with her. I like her.
没问题  大家随意  随意
That's fine. Go with your instincts!
那我做什么呢
What am I doing again?
拜托你们  专心一点
Come on, would you please pay attention.
我随时都会醒来
I could wake up at any moment.
我是约书亚  我来接瑞秋
I'm Joshua. I'm here to pick up Rachel.
他可不是约书亚
No, no, no. That's not Joshua.
别要求太高  我又没见过他
What do you want from me? I never met the guy.
瑞秋  真可惜你要走了
So, anyway, Rachel, I'm sorry you can't stay.
我们还有很多事要忙
The rest of us have a lot of work to do.
你干什么
What are you doing?
算了  我还是赶紧醒过来吧
All right, listen. I got to wake up.